<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Trip</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://deanmv.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://deanmv.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 20:24:01 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 20:24:01 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are We There Yet?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Not going to lie, today dragged! Knowing we had nothing to see along the way and it’s part 1 of our drive to Chicago. 503.6 miles basically across one road! Thank goodness American cars have cruise control :D The first hour and a half was through snow! Who’d have thought it? It was SO heavy, made us look like tits driving in a Mustang when everyone in South Dakota had pick up trucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/usDrive.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 6 hours into the drive we spotted a sign of the Green Giant statue, 60ft high! Obviously, we had to stop and I needed a picture with it. No idea why it was there (Dean obviously stopped to read all the signs…).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/greenGiant.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We checked into yet another hotel and went for dinner at Applebees, it was amazing! Such nice food although midway through a burger slider I realised it had pineapple in (I’m allergic!), this honeymoon could get interesting :/
On the plus side, they played some classic music, Green Day and All American Rejects and the Margaritas were delicious!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re settled in for the night now watching trash US telly, Locked Up! Got obsessed with it a few years ago in Vegas :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
503.6 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
6 Hours 53 Minutes and 08 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/09/Are-We-There-Yet%3F.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/09/Are-We-There-Yet%3F.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s Not As Big As I Thought</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we’re back in Mustang Mitch (Yeah, obviously we named him) en route to Mount Rushmore. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/driveToRushmore.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The towns nearby were incredible, one was called Pringle and only 157 people lived there! The drive up to Mount Rushmore was very scenic and reminded us of Yosemite. With much anticipation, I filmed the drive up the mountain waiting to see the sculptures and suddenly… there they were… tiny. I know it sounds stupid as they are MASSIVE but it didn’t seem it. It just wasn’t as impressive as I expected. Dean was annoyed I didn’t appreciate the scale of them and went off reading every single information sign… &lt;em&gt;yawn&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rushmore.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was an interesting film in the Theatre about the making of them, which I did find interesting as I didn’t realise it took so long to build! I am glad obviously that we went to see them :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After driving to another hotel for the night (which seems like luxury compared to the hell hole we stayed in last night) we’re off for pizza! Tomorrow is part 1 of the drive to Chicago, doesn’t look like there is anything a long the way so don’t expect a post!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
399.1 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
6 Hours 24 Minutes and 51 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/08/Its-Not-As-Big-As-I-Thought.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/08/Its-Not-As-Big-As-I-Thought.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Got The Wrong Room Bro</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Grabbed an Uber (taxi) into the centre of Denver today and got a Starbucks for breakfast (so we could use their WiFi). Took a stroll around and realised Denver is extremely dull at 9am… We then remembered the Zoo! Love a good zoo and this one was huge!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/zoo1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/zoo2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/zoo3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We spent almost 4 hours at the zoo wondering round, turns out American kids are crazy loud! Once the school trips had left we could enjoy the zoo in peace and even managed a selfie with the lions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/zoo4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/zoo5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got an Uber back to town and found a cocktail bar offering Champagne cocktails for $4 on their happy hour… day made! To top the day off, we went to the Cheesecake factory for dinner! Typically, we filled up on the dinner and couldn’t manage a cheesecake (although still ordered one for take out to have for breakfast).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to lying down after a big meal, we headed back to the motel. Opened the door to find 3 men in our room! One of which said ‘you got the wrong room bro’… no, we definitely didn’t!!! Where the hell was our stuff?!!!!!! Panicking and running to the reception to ask what’s happened, they were just as confused but thankfully had our things. I full on panicked wondering where the hell my wedding dress was!!!!!!! The receptionist was kind enough to honour our booking (as it was their fault giving away our room!) and we managed to blag free WiFi too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Safe to say, we are heading out as early as possible to get away from this hotel. Long drive to Rushmore before staying in a (hopefully nicer) hotel in Rapid City tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
0 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
0 Hours 0 Minutes and 0 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays Walking:&lt;br /&gt;
8.6 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
3 Hours and 2 Minutes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/07/You-Got-The-Wrong-Room-Bro.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/07/You-Got-The-Wrong-Room-Bro.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What time is it now?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Breakfast with a view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/breakfastView.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Driving to The View Hotel lost us an hour due to them not in keeping with DST. We left at 8:30am and by 8:45am we gained the hour back which totally threw us, now it was 7:45am! Who the hell are we leaving so early?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We planned a long day ahead to save us a days driving tomorrow so we could explore Denver. Those that know me well enough know I’m a complete backseat driver, so to be in the 2nd day of driving we’ve done well to not yell at each other! After stopping to take a badass picture of the Mustang we continued ahead with the roof down (note to self… don’t have your hair down when the roof is off! SO many knots - Me, not Dean! :P).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/LoMustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along the way, we booked a hotel just outside Denver for the next two nights. SO glad we’re with 3 and can use our phone as normal (Other phone providers are available… they’re just not as good). Then, the rain hit! Bloody hell does it rain here. This didn’t help my blisters when driving, I couldn’t have gripped harder to the steering wheel if I’d tried! Not to mention driving along the steepest cliff edges (Holz, you would have HATED it!). Somewhere across the morning we lost an hour again! I can’t keep up, too confused!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next stop, Wendy’s! The waitress needed my name for the order so I said Lois and without fail she typed it… RIGHT! This is why I love the USA, they never look in horror when I say my name and hope I automatically start spelling it. After filling up with more petrol and Dean back at the wheel and just over 2 hours left of the drive, we drove through some snowy mountains. Dean tried to persuade me to let us stop and ski… it wasn’t happening - bossy wife. Along the route, we drove up 12,000ft and ended up driving through clouds and snow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/snow.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our only complaint about the Mustang is the seats! After a few hours your back kills where the seat digs in. Looking forward to a days break tomorrow and some WALKING around. After checking into a hotel that I’m sure featured in Psycho, we grabbed some booze from the liquor store and settled in for the night watching the thunderstorm and hoping the Mustang doesn’t get nicked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
501 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
8 Hours 54 Minutes and 41 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/06/What-Time-Is-It-Now.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/06/What-Time-Is-It-Now.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mustang Sally</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Elvis has left the building… Today, we left Vegas! After picking up a badass MUSTANG and struggling to fit our suitcases in (we had to take the roof down to fit one in the back seat!) we hit the road. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En route to The View hotel in Monument Valley, roughly 6.5 hours away from Vegas, Dean started the drive. His little face lit up when the car started with a press of a button and all things gadgety appeared on the screen. We have our road trip Spotify playlist on the go to keep us entertained as well as the fantastic scenery. Honestly, why can’t the UK look more like the US? Views for miles and miles, empty roads, sunshine and us tourists not really sure what we’re doing! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First pit stop was a giggle, not only did we not know whether the car was Petrol or Diesel, but we couldn’t figure out the pump! Thankfully, the lady at the gas station was very helpful. Back on the road with me at the wheel… terrified! Who let me drive a basically new Mustang on the other side of the road and over a very sketchy looking bridge! After several hours we switched back, I gave myself blisters from gripping on to the steering wheel so tightly! Dean was glad to be driving again, he didn’t even want to let me have a turn… big kid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we arrive in Monument Valley and it’s bloody raining! However, The View Hotel is insaaaane. We have a massive room with a microwave; which I mistook to be a TV… it’s been a long day! Our own private balcony which has an amazing view (see below).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/TheView.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Off to go get dinner overlooking this view and see if we can find any munch for the drive tomorrow! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
399.6 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
6 Hours 52 Minutes and 46 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/05/Mustang-Sally.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/05/Mustang-Sally.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paris, Las Vegas</title>
        <description>&lt;video autoplay loop controls&gt;
	&lt;source src=&quot;/videos/Paris.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot;&gt;
	&lt;source src=&quot;/videos/Paris.webm&quot; type=&quot;video/webm&quot;&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vegas Baby! So, we arrive amidst the big fight chaos and in a rush to get to the Marriage License Bureau we found ourselves stuck in traffic! Thankfully, we were there before they shut and got our license :)&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;By morning, we hear there was a shooting at the hotel just next door... glad we didn’t attempt to go the MGM and watch the fight in their sports bar as it was 150$ just to get in to watch it on the TV’s!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By 11am we started getting ready for the big day! With some bubbly and beer for dutch courage we dolled up. At 1 o’clock the limo driver called to pick us up... no going back now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we arrived at the Shalimar Wedding Chapel we filled out paperwork and waited for the Minister after having some pictures taken. Just a short 3 minute ceremony and suddenly we are Mr and Mrs Vizer :) Everyone was lovely and it was perfect, not too much fuss as we aren’t ones for showing off! After getting taken back to the Paris hotel in the limo there was enough time for a quick gamble in our wedding gear before getting ready for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Eiffel Tower Restaurant was fantastic and the staff were kind enough to give us the window seat over looking the Bellagio fountains and a free celebratory dessert :D (note to self: tell everyone we’ve just gotten married to get ALL THE FREEBIES).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://scontent.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-xpt1/v/t1.0-9/11110256_10152698907851682_5019392800112975303_n.jpg?oh=bdadb30d4a705c83073d8137fc050efe&amp;oe=55E55666&quot; /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right, time to pack as we have an early start to pick up the car and drive to our first stop, The View hotel in Monument Valley! Mrs Vizer... xx&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 04:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/04/Paris-Las-Vegas.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/04/Paris-Las-Vegas.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Things To Do</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;las-vegas&quot;&gt;Las Vegas&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.caesars.com/paris-las-vegas/restaurants/eiffel-tower-restaurant&quot;&gt;Eiffel Tower Restaurant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://vegasexperience.com/&quot;&gt;Fremont Street&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;clear-creek-county&quot;&gt;Clear Creek County&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://clearcreekcounty.org/trip-ideas/&quot;&gt;Guanella Pass Fall Spectacular&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://clearcreekcounty.org/horse-riding/&quot;&gt;Horse Riding&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://clearcreekcounty.org/colorado-sport-atv-riders/&quot;&gt;ATV Riding&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;denver&quot;&gt;Denver&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.denver.org/listings/Coors-Brewery-Tours---MillerCoors/3875/&quot;&gt;Coors Brewery Tour&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.denver.org/listings/16th-Street-Mall---Pedestrian-Mall/4249/&quot;&gt;16th Street Mall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rapid-city&quot;&gt;Rapid City&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.visitrapidcity.com/things-to-do/mount-rushmore&quot;&gt;Mount Rushmore&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;chicago&quot;&gt;Chicago&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theskydeck.com/&quot;&gt;The Sky Deck&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sheddaquarium.org/&quot;&gt;Shedd Aquarium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cityofchicago.org/city/en/depts/dca/supp_info/millennium_park_-artarchitecture.html&quot;&gt;Millennium Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;cleveland&quot;&gt;Cleveland&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;washington&quot;&gt;Washington&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/1600&quot;&gt;The White House&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://washington.org/DC-guide-to/washington-monument&quot;&gt;The Washington Monument&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://washington.org/DC-guide-to/lincoln-memorial&quot;&gt;The Lincoln Memorial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://washington.org/DC-guide-to/jefferson-memorial&quot;&gt;The Jefferson Memorial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;philadelphia&quot;&gt;Philadelphia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.delawareriverwaterfront.com/places/spruce-street-harbor-park&quot;&gt;Spruce Street Harbour Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.phillymagicgardens.org/&quot;&gt;Philadelphia’s Magic Gardens&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-york&quot;&gt;New York&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rockefellercenter.com&quot;&gt;Rockefeller Center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nypl.org/&quot;&gt;New York Public Library&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/04/01/Things-To-Do.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/04/01/Things-To-Do.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Trip in Numbers</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;numberSection&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div&gt;
		&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-2x fa-plane&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
		&lt;h2&gt;LGW to LAS&lt;/h2&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;5,321 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
		10 hours and 30 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;div&gt;
		&lt;h2&gt;JFK to LGW&lt;/h2&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;3,464 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
		7 hours and 26 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;numberSection&quot;&gt;
	&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-2x fa-car&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;3,361 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
	60 hours and 14 minutes&lt;br /&gt;
	~$700 in fuel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;numberSection&quot;&gt;
	&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-2x fa-map-marker&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;13 States&lt;br /&gt;
	10 Cities&lt;br /&gt;
	4 Major Landmarks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;numberSection&quot;&gt;
	&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-2x fa-glass&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &amp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-2x fa-cutlery&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;26 meals from gas stations&lt;br /&gt;
	10 bottles of champagne to be consumed&lt;br /&gt;
	11 hotel mini fridges to be raided&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/03/29/The-Trip-In-Numbers.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/03/29/The-Trip-In-Numbers.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Plan</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-1-3&quot;&gt;Day 1-3&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Paris Hotel - Las Vegas
&lt;img src=&quot;http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9f/Las_vegas_hotel_paris.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-4&quot;&gt;Day 4&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Las Vegas - The View Hotel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.darngooddigs.com/photos/theview2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-5&quot;&gt;Day 5&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The View Hotel - Clear Creek County, Colorado&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://clearcreekcounty.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/mount-evans-scenic-drive1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-6&quot;&gt;Day 6&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clear Creek County, Colorado - Denver, Colorado&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://synoptek.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/denvercity.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-7&quot;&gt;Day 7&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Denver, Colorado&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.ecampervanhire.com/wp-content/uploads/denver-colorado.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-8&quot;&gt;Day 8&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Denver, Colorado - Mount Rushmore, South Dakota - Rapid City, South Dakota&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://travel.sndimg.com/static_files/imagesource/imageoutput6/mt-rushmore_966x543.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-9&quot;&gt;Day 9&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rapid City, South Dakota - Albert Lea, Minnesota&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://images.topix.com/gallery/up-JSDMKE4KIGPFFQ1D.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-10&quot;&gt;Day 10&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Albert Lea, Minnesota - Chicago, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.photographyblogger.net/wp-content/uploads/2009/09/Chicago4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-11&quot;&gt;Day 11&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chicago, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.charterflightgroup.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/Chicago-IL.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-12&quot;&gt;Day 12&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chicago, Illinois - Cleveland, Ohio&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.destination360.com/north-america/us/ohio/images/s/cleveland.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-13&quot;&gt;Day 13&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cleveland, Ohio - Washington, DC&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://etadventures.com/city_images/132164119557.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-14&quot;&gt;Day 14&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Washington, DC&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://bethesda.hyatt.com/content/dam/Multimedia/park/wasph/737x415xWASPH_P086_Lincoln_Memorial_1280x720_54628.jpg.pagespeed.ic.vpBfHKFZbE.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-15&quot;&gt;Day 15&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Washington, DC - Philadelphia, Pensilvania&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.suitqaisdiaries.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/pl0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-16&quot;&gt;Day 16&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Philadelphia, Pensilvania - New York, New York&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/03/9b/2d/f2/new-york-city.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-17-19&quot;&gt;Day 17-19&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cassy Hotel, New York&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://s3.amazonaws.com/s3aws.getaroom.com/property_images/623bcc3f-1024-4d55-8ed2-a650d37feb64/cassa_night-36-editsm_grid_12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 03:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/01/22/The-Plan.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/01/22/The-Plan.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
