<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Trip</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://deanmv.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://deanmv.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 18:01:42 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 18:01:42 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Whole Lot Of Selfies</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Spent the day being tourists in sunny sunny Washington DC. We walked past the White House again and over to the Washington Monument before heading over to the Lincoln Memorial. Where ever we seem to go at the moment we are surrounded by bus loads of school kids! FYI American kids are way more annoying than UK kids, they’re SO loud! As we made our way up the steps by the Lincoln Memorial, the amount of selfie sticks tripled. People appear to have no self awareness when it comes to taking selfies. Is it really the right time and place to take a selfie at the war memorial or with Lincoln in the background? Don’t get me started on the amount of effort some people go to prior to taking the selfie. I can’t wait for the day people look back and say ‘why the hell did we used to have our phones on a stick?’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Monument.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Lincoln.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I had my first Five Guys burger today! It was lush, easily the best burger I’ve had. Don’t know why Basingstoke doesn’t have one! Speaking of food, we’ve found a Nandos here so it’s only right we grab a ‘cheeky Nandos’ for dinner :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve walked a crazy amount today, so much so I needed a nap when we got back to the hotel. That and it’s been so hot I got a headache and being a typical Brit I got a little sunburnt :( &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve enjoyed Washington DC, not too crowded and much more of a relaxing city than NYC but I’ve found it a little too wealthy. We wanted to stop off for a drink on our way back from the memorials but everywhere seemed far too posh and expensive! Off to Philadelphia tomorrow morning, looking forward to seeing everything!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays Walk:&lt;br /&gt;
9.8 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
3 Hours 45 Minutes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/14/A-Whole-Lot-Of-Selfies.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/14/A-Whole-Lot-Of-Selfies.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two Krispy Kremes And A Whole Lot Of Skittles</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After getting almost no sleep due to the people next door coughing/choking all night and slamming doors, we left early to head to Washington DC! Accidentally missed breakfast so settled for Krispy Kreme doughnuts and a LOT of Skittles :D Balanced diet of course. Don’t think we’ve had/seen any fruit and veg the whole time we’ve been here! Actually that’s a lie, Dean had lettuce and tomatoes in his Subway this afternoon… that counts, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s getting frustrating how many Americans don’t seem to be able to understand us. Yes, we phrase things slightly differently but you speak OUR language! We keep having to repeat ourselves then giving up and phrasing differently (i.e. dumbing down) for the Americans to understand ;) Dean was told he sounded Canadian today and when Dean corrected him the guy said ‘If you’d thrown an ‘aye’ in every now and then I’d have thought you were Canadian for sure!’ :’)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SUCCESS! My Wedding dress still fits after a week and a half of American food! Only one more week to go, fingers crossed it’ll still fit! :) Speaking of food, we went out for delicious Asian food tonight. Our waiter was very skinny (clearly never eaten Asian food in his life) but the food was delicious!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Food.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Food2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We needed a walk after the big dinner so leisurely strolled to the White House (as you do). Something seemed to be going on as there were a lot of Police and the whole park was taped off. Eventually, they opened the park again and we were lead down to the White House by Secret Service on our own little tour :D Didn’t spot Barack though… let down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Whitehouse.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We then had drinks at the bar in the hotel and got chatting to the locals. Turns out the man we were chatting to casually lived in Vegas for tax avoidance purposes (who tells strangers this?!) and the barmaid watches Top Gear and ‘Ello ‘Ello… She was lovely and gave us two free drinks as it’s our honeymoon, clearly it does pay off telling people!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
348.9 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
6 Hours 37 Minutes 28 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/13/Two-Krispy-Kremes-And-A-Whole-Lot-Of-Skittles!.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/13/Two-Krispy-Kremes-And-A-Whole-Lot-Of-Skittles!.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Is That Girl Stretching In Burger King?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;8 years ago today, Dean awkwardly asked me out over MSN to Jet - Are You Gunna Be My Girl? lyrics. Who’d have thought 8 years later we’d be home owners, married and driving across America! We’re still yet to have our first argument (as I’m always right ;) ).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To celebrate, we’re spending 6 hours in the car, lol. It’s all worth it though as we make our way to Washington. It’s nice to not have much walking to do today as my legs and hips are aching from yesterdays 8 miles! I’ve convinced Dean to let me buy a new pair of Uggs too as the shoes I bought with me are soaked and not particularly good to walk long distances in… what a shame, new Uggs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other news, we’re in the middle of making a video of our trip. We’re onto 3rd song so far, might be a long video :/ We planned to film us getting ready on our Wedding day but if we’re honest we both were crapping ourselves and completely forgot! Nevertheless, it’s still a good video so far with lots of random clips of things we’ve done/seen :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Checking into yet another hotel, unpacking my dress again in the hope it doesn’t crease too much and off to grab yet more food! Up early to finish the drive to Washington DC :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
340.9 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
5 Hours 19 Minutes 56 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/12/Why-Is-That-Girl-Stretching-In-Burger-King%3F.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/12/Why-Is-That-Girl-Stretching-In-Burger-King%3F.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chicago</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night, we had THE pizza from Man Vs Food. It was insane! Took an hour to cook (was well worth it) as it is 3” deep and FULL of deliciousness. We had the BBQ Beef pizza with peppers and onions. It was so filling I could only manage one slice… The waitress looked appalled at our failed attempt, however it made a good breakfast this morning! We also took a nice stroll round the park and discovered lots of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bean.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/chicagoMiniPlanet.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today… Dean had his first coffee! I say coffee, it was a caffe mocha but it was enough to have him buzzing ;) We whizzed round the Field Natural History Museum before visiting the Aquarium. We saw the worlds most complete T Rex dinosaur which was huge, just her (they’ve named it Sue after the lady that discovered it) skull weighed 600lbs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aquarium was huge! We got to watch a ‘show’ which was really good with Dolphins showing off their skills. Although, I found the rave music and lighting a little unnecessary. When we left to walk back to the hotel we got caught in the storm! We were soaked and along the way we found someones wallet. After finding a camera at Mount Rushmore and being good people by handing it in, we thought we’d do the same with the wallet… Turns out no one wanted to help! After asking 3 different people we managed to leave it with a reluctant security guard at the college the guy goes to (found a little info in the wallet - we also tried to search him on Facebook first!). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On to the Willis tower and the Sky Deck. Dean has been excited to walk out on the glass platform… me, not so much! We eventually got to the front of the queue and walked out on the platform. It wasn’t as scary as I’d imagined, but I didn’t want to stay for long! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/skyDeck.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’d walked so much today that we’d built up an appetite for dinner! We stumbled across Noodles &amp;amp; Company and oh my god was it a good find :D So cheap but all fresh and cooked to order. We need places like this in the UK!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, we start the drive to Washington and are staying the night in Richfield. Turns out the hotels get more and more expensive the further across we are driving! :/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays walking:&lt;br /&gt;
8 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
3 Hours 36 Minutes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/11/Chicago.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/11/Chicago.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do The Amish Have Ovens?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was a big day… Chicago!! We’ve both been looking forward to getting here so we set off early (thanks to a man and his noisy barking dog outside our hotel room) and hit the road. I started the drive so Dean could take over when it came to driving through Chicago. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;America seems to have a crazy amount of billboards, like a dangerous amount when you should be concentrating on driving. We drove past a sign for ‘Amish Ovens’ which confused me as I didn’t think they could have ovens… Dean just laughed at me, obviously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stopped off at McDonalds for lunch… it was the strangest McDonalds I’ve ever seen! Set in a winter ski lodge basically with stuffed animals everywhere and people sitting around an un-lit fire eating McDonalds. Kids wandering in swimming costumes and a games room… It didn’t quite add up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then came the final part of the trip to Chicago! Traffic began to build along with the amount of tolls, we went through 4! Why not just charge more at one? I was a classic Brit and gave the wrong coins as no matter how many times we’ve visited the US I still can’t tell what coin is what.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/cloudyChicago.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually we saw the foggy Chicago skyline, we’re here! Can’t wait to look around this city :D We drove our Mustang to the valet parking like the ‘ballers’ we are (according to Dean) and had our luggage taken to our room (seriously, what have we become?). Tonight, we’ll explore and eat deep pan Chicago pizza! Hoping to find the place that featured on Man Vs Food :D * must remember I still need to fit into my wedding dress for the 23rd! *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/chicagoHotelView.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
405 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
6 Hours 25 Minutes and 08 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/10/Do-The-Amish-Have-Ovens%3F.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/10/Do-The-Amish-Have-Ovens%3F.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are We There Yet?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Not going to lie, today dragged! Knowing we had nothing to see along the way and it’s part 1 of our drive to Chicago. 503.6 miles basically across one road! Thank goodness American cars have cruise control :D The first hour and a half was through snow! Who’d have thought it? It was SO heavy, made us look like tits driving in a Mustang when everyone in South Dakota had pick up trucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/usDrive.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 6 hours into the drive we spotted a sign of the Green Giant statue, 60ft high! Obviously, we had to stop and I needed a picture with it. No idea why it was there (Dean obviously stopped to read all the signs…).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/greenGiant.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We checked into yet another hotel and went for dinner at Applebees, it was amazing! Such nice food although midway through a burger slider I realised it had pineapple in (I’m allergic!), this honeymoon could get interesting :/
On the plus side, they played some classic music, Green Day and All American Rejects and the Margaritas were delicious!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re settled in for the night now watching trash US telly, Locked Up! Got obsessed with it a few years ago in Vegas :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
503.6 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
6 Hours 53 Minutes and 08 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/09/Are-We-There-Yet%3F.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/09/Are-We-There-Yet%3F.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s Not As Big As I Thought</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we’re back in Mustang Mitch (Yeah, obviously we named him) en route to Mount Rushmore. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/driveToRushmore.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The towns nearby were incredible, one was called Pringle and only 157 people lived there! The drive up to Mount Rushmore was very scenic and reminded us of Yosemite. With much anticipation, I filmed the drive up the mountain waiting to see the sculptures and suddenly… there they were… tiny. I know it sounds stupid as they are MASSIVE but it didn’t seem it. It just wasn’t as impressive as I expected. Dean was annoyed I didn’t appreciate the scale of them and went off reading every single information sign… &lt;em&gt;yawn&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/rushmore.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was an interesting film in the Theatre about the making of them, which I did find interesting as I didn’t realise it took so long to build! I am glad obviously that we went to see them :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After driving to another hotel for the night (which seems like luxury compared to the hell hole we stayed in last night) we’re off for pizza! Tomorrow is part 1 of the drive to Chicago, doesn’t look like there is anything a long the way so don’t expect a post!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
399.1 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
6 Hours 24 Minutes and 51 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/08/Its-Not-As-Big-As-I-Thought.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/08/Its-Not-As-Big-As-I-Thought.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Got The Wrong Room Bro</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Grabbed an Uber (taxi) into the centre of Denver today and got a Starbucks for breakfast (so we could use their WiFi). Took a stroll around and realised Denver is extremely dull at 9am… We then remembered the Zoo! Love a good zoo and this one was huge!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/zoo1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/zoo2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/zoo3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We spent almost 4 hours at the zoo wondering round, turns out American kids are crazy loud! Once the school trips had left we could enjoy the zoo in peace and even managed a selfie with the lions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/zoo4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/zoo5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got an Uber back to town and found a cocktail bar offering Champagne cocktails for $4 on their happy hour… day made! To top the day off, we went to the Cheesecake factory for dinner! Typically, we filled up on the dinner and couldn’t manage a cheesecake (although still ordered one for take out to have for breakfast).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to lying down after a big meal, we headed back to the motel. Opened the door to find 3 men in our room! One of which said ‘you got the wrong room bro’… no, we definitely didn’t!!! Where the hell was our stuff?!!!!!! Panicking and running to the reception to ask what’s happened, they were just as confused but thankfully had our things. I full on panicked wondering where the hell my wedding dress was!!!!!!! The receptionist was kind enough to honour our booking (as it was their fault giving away our room!) and we managed to blag free WiFi too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Safe to say, we are heading out as early as possible to get away from this hotel. Long drive to Rushmore before staying in a (hopefully nicer) hotel in Rapid City tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
0 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
0 Hours 0 Minutes and 0 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays Walking:&lt;br /&gt;
8.6 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
3 Hours and 2 Minutes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/07/You-Got-The-Wrong-Room-Bro.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/07/You-Got-The-Wrong-Room-Bro.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What time is it now?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Breakfast with a view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/breakfastView.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Driving to The View Hotel lost us an hour due to them not in keeping with DST. We left at 8:30am and by 8:45am we gained the hour back which totally threw us, now it was 7:45am! Who the hell are we leaving so early?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We planned a long day ahead to save us a days driving tomorrow so we could explore Denver. Those that know me well enough know I’m a complete backseat driver, so to be in the 2nd day of driving we’ve done well to not yell at each other! After stopping to take a badass picture of the Mustang we continued ahead with the roof down (note to self… don’t have your hair down when the roof is off! SO many knots - Me, not Dean! :P).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/LoMustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along the way, we booked a hotel just outside Denver for the next two nights. SO glad we’re with 3 and can use our phone as normal (Other phone providers are available… they’re just not as good). Then, the rain hit! Bloody hell does it rain here. This didn’t help my blisters when driving, I couldn’t have gripped harder to the steering wheel if I’d tried! Not to mention driving along the steepest cliff edges (Holz, you would have HATED it!). Somewhere across the morning we lost an hour again! I can’t keep up, too confused!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next stop, Wendy’s! The waitress needed my name for the order so I said Lois and without fail she typed it… RIGHT! This is why I love the USA, they never look in horror when I say my name and hope I automatically start spelling it. After filling up with more petrol and Dean back at the wheel and just over 2 hours left of the drive, we drove through some snowy mountains. Dean tried to persuade me to let us stop and ski… it wasn’t happening - bossy wife. Along the route, we drove up 12,000ft and ended up driving through clouds and snow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/snow.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our only complaint about the Mustang is the seats! After a few hours your back kills where the seat digs in. Looking forward to a days break tomorrow and some WALKING around. After checking into a hotel that I’m sure featured in Psycho, we grabbed some booze from the liquor store and settled in for the night watching the thunderstorm and hoping the Mustang doesn’t get nicked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
501 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
8 Hours 54 Minutes and 41 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/06/What-Time-Is-It-Now.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/06/What-Time-Is-It-Now.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mustang Sally</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Elvis has left the building… Today, we left Vegas! After picking up a badass MUSTANG and struggling to fit our suitcases in (we had to take the roof down to fit one in the back seat!) we hit the road. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/mustang.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En route to The View hotel in Monument Valley, roughly 6.5 hours away from Vegas, Dean started the drive. His little face lit up when the car started with a press of a button and all things gadgety appeared on the screen. We have our road trip Spotify playlist on the go to keep us entertained as well as the fantastic scenery. Honestly, why can’t the UK look more like the US? Views for miles and miles, empty roads, sunshine and us tourists not really sure what we’re doing! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First pit stop was a giggle, not only did we not know whether the car was Petrol or Diesel, but we couldn’t figure out the pump! Thankfully, the lady at the gas station was very helpful. Back on the road with me at the wheel… terrified! Who let me drive a basically new Mustang on the other side of the road and over a very sketchy looking bridge! After several hours we switched back, I gave myself blisters from gripping on to the steering wheel so tightly! Dean was glad to be driving again, he didn’t even want to let me have a turn… big kid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we arrive in Monument Valley and it’s bloody raining! However, The View Hotel is insaaaane. We have a massive room with a microwave; which I mistook to be a TV… it’s been a long day! Our own private balcony which has an amazing view (see below).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/TheView.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Off to go get dinner overlooking this view and see if we can find any munch for the drive tomorrow! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todays drive:&lt;br /&gt;
399.6 Miles&lt;br /&gt;
6 Hours 52 Minutes and 46 Seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vizers xx&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 05:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/05/Mustang-Sally.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://deanmv.github.io/2015/05/05/Mustang-Sally.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
